Finding Aid for Board of Regents (University of Michigan) Records 1817-2011
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Exhibits of the Regents Meetings, 1899-1987
  - 1911-1920
    - June 22, 1915
      - Y-EEE (Box 9)
    - July 22, 1915
      - Draft Minutes and A-F 1/2 (Box 9)
      - F 3/4-AAA (Box 9)
    - October 15, 1915 (Box 9)
    - November 2, 1915 (Box 9)
    - December 1, 1915 (Box 9)
    - January 6, 1916 (Box 9)
    - February 11, 1916 (Box 9)
    - March 1, 1916 (Box 9)
    - April 6, 1916 (Box 10)
      - Draft Minutes and A-O (Box 10)
      - P-QQQ (Box 10)
    - May 19, 1916
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 10)
      - J-DDDD (Box 10)
    - June 27, 1916
      - Draft Minutes and A-T (Box 10)
      - U-CCCC (Box 10)
    - July 19, 1916
      - Draft Minutes and A (Box 10)
      - B-XX (Box 10)
    - October 13, 1916
      - Draft Minutes and A-AA (Box 10)
      - BB-JJJJ (Box 10)
    - November 24, 1916
      - Draft Minutes and A-II (Box 10)
      - JJ-AAAA (Box 10)
    - December 22, 1916
      - Draft Minutes and A-M (Box 10)
      - N-YY (Box 10)
    - January 19, 1917 (Box 10)
    - February 23, 1917 (Box 10)
    - March 30, 1917 (Box 10)
    - April 27, 1917 (Box 11)
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 11)
      - F-KK (Box 11)
    - May 31, 1917
      - Draft Minutes and A-P (Box 11)
      - Q-RRR (Box 11)
    - June 22, 1917 (Box 11)
    - June 26, 1917 (Box 11)
    - July 20, 1917 (Box 11)
    - October 12, 1917
      - Draft Minutes and A-Z (Box 11)
      - AA-ZZZZ (Box 11)
    - November 16, 1917
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 11)
      - K-J2 (Box 11)
    - December 21, 1917
      - Draft Minutes and A-Y (Box 11)
      - Z-V1 (Box 11)
    - January 17, 1918 (Box 11)
    - February 21, 1918 (Box 11)
    - April 5, 1918
      - Draft Minutes and A-O (Box 11)
      - P-Q3 (Box 11)
    - May 3, 1918 (Box 11)
    - June 14, 1918 (Box 12)
      - Draft Minutes and A-S (Box 12)
      - T-C4 (Box 12)
    - June 25, 1918 (Box 12)
    - July 19, 1918 (Box 12)
    - August 23, 1918 (Box 12)
    - October 25, 1918
      - Draft Minutes and A-Z (Box 12)
      - A2-C4 (Box 12)
    - November 22, 1918
      - Draft Minutes and A-Q (Box 12)
      - R-P2 (Box 12)
    - December 13, 1918 (Box 12)
    - January 10, 1919 (Box 12)
    - February 28, 1919
      - Draft Minutes and A-D2 (Box 12)
      - E2-M3 (Box 12)
    - March 12, 1919 (Box 12)
    - April 25, 1919
      - Draft Minutes and A-E2 (Box 12)
      - F2-U3 (Box 12)
    - May 9, 1919 (Box 12)
    - May 23, 1919 (Box 12)
    - May 28, 1919 (Box 12)
    - June 13, 1919 (Box 12)
    - June 24, 1919 (Box 12)
    - June 26, 1919 (Box 13)
    - August 6, 1919 (Box 13)
    - September 26, 1919
      - Draft Minutes and A-V (Box 13)
      - W-W3 (Box 13)
    - October 17, 1919 (Box 13)
    - November 21, 1919
      - Draft Minutes and A-F2 (Box 13)
      - G2-L3 (Box 13)
    - December 19, 1919 (Box 13)
    - January 8, 1920 (Box 13)
    - February 20, 1920 (Box 13)
    - March 12, 1920
      - Draft Minutes and A-S2 (Box 13)
      - T2-K3 (Box 13)
    - March 26, 1920 (Box 13)
    - April 30, 1920
      - Draft Minutes and A-Z (Box 13)
      - A2-P3 (Box 13)
    - May 28, 1920 (Box 13)
    - June 18, 1920 (Box 13)
    - June 22, 1920 (Box 14)
    - July 23, 1920
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 14)
      - E-L3 (Box 14)
    - September 11, 1920 (Box 14)
    - October 1, 1920 (Box 14)
    - November 3, 1920 (Box 14)
    - December 3, 1920 (Box 14)
  - 1921-1930
    - January 7, 1921 (Box 14)
    - February 10, 1921
      - Draft Minutes and A (Box 14)
      - B-H3 (Box 14)
    - March 25, 1921 (Box 14)
    - April 29, 1921 (Box 14)
    - May 27, 1921 (Box 14)
    - June 22, 1921 (Box 14)
    - June 28, 1921 (Box 14)
    - September 30, 1921
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 14)
      - E-U3 (Box 14)
    - October 28, 1921 (Box 15)
    - December 9, 1921
      - Draft Minutes and A-Q (Box 15)
      - R-Q3 (Box 15)
    - January 27, 1922 (Box 15)
    - February 24, 1922 (Box 15)
    - March 15, 1922 (Box 15)
    - March 31, 1922
      - Draft Minutes and A-A2 (Box 15)
      - B2-C4 (Box 15)
    - April 28, 1922
      - Draft Minutes and A-K (Box 15)
      - L-H3 (Box 15)
    - May 26, 1922 (Box 15)
    - June 16, 1922 (Box 15)
    - June 28, 1922
      - Draft Minutes and A-E2 (Box 15)
      - F2-M3 (Box 15)
    - September 29, 1922
      - Draft Minutes and A-Q (Box 15)
      - R-M4 (Box 15)
    - October 27, 1922 (Box 16)
    - November 24, 1922 (Box 16)
    - December 22, 1922
      - Draft Minutes and A-D2 (Box 16)
      - E2-T3 (Box 16)
    - January 26, 1923 (Box 16)
    - February 23, 1923 (Box 16)
    - March 29, 1923
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 16)
      - D-E3 (Box 16)
    - April 27, 1923 (Box 16)
    - May 25, 1923
      - Draft Minutes and A-D2 (Box 16)
      - E2-J4 (Box 16)
    - June 14, 1923
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 16)
      - E-B3 (Box 16)
      - C3-V4 (Box 16)
    - September 28, 1923
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 16)
      - F-Z (Box 16)
      - A2-H3 (Box 17)
      - I3-J5 (Box 17)
    - October 26, 1923
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 17)
      - E-Z (Box 17)
      - A2-A4 (Box 17)
    - November 23, 1923
      - Draft Minutes and A-Z (Box 17)
      - A2-C3 (Box 17)
    - December 21, 1923 (Box 17)
    - January 25, 1924 (Box 17)
    - February 12, 1924 (Box 17)
    - February 29, 1924
      - Draft Minutes and A-I2 (Box 17)
      - J2-X4 (Box 17)
    - March 28, 1924
      - Draft Minutes and A-Z2 (Box 17)
      - A3-U3 (Box 17)
    - April 24, 1924
      - Draft Minutes and A-Z (Box 17)
      - A2-Z3 (Box 17)
    - May 29, 1924
      - Draft Minutes and A-X (Box 17)
      - Y-L4 (Box 17)
    - June 13, 1924 (Box 18)
    - September 26, 1924
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 18)
      - J-E2 (Box 18)
      - F2-P3 (Box 18)
      - Q3-V4 (Box 18)
    - October 25, 1924
      - Draft Minutes and A-D2 (Box 18)
      - E2-M3 (Box 18)
    - November 21, 1924
      - Draft Minutes and A-P2 (Box 18)
      - Q-2-S3 (Box 18)
    - December 19, 1924 (Box 18)
    - January 30, 1925
      - Draft Minutes and A-R2 (Box 18)
      - S2-N4 (Box 18)
    - February 27, 1925 (Box 18)
    - March 27, 1925 (Box 18)
    - April 24, 1925 (Box 18)
    - May 28, 1925 (Box 18)
    - June 12, 1925 (Box 19)
      - Draft Minutes and A-Q (Box 19)
      - R-N2 (Box 19)
    - September 10, 1925 (Box 19)
    - September 24, 1925
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 19)
      - E2-D3 (Box 19)
    - October 30, 1925
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 19)
      - F-I3 (Box 19)
    - November 20, 1925 (Box 19)
    - December 18, 1925 (Box 19)
    - January 28, 1926 (Box 19)
    - February 25, 1926 (Box 19)
    - March 24, 1926 (Box 19)
    - April 22, 1926 (Box 19)
    - May 27, 1926 (Box 19)
    - June 11, 1926
      - Draft Minutes and A-X (Box 19)
      - Y-L3 (Box 19)
    - September 23, 1926
      - Draft Minutes and A-Q2 (Box 19)
      - R2-N3 (Box 20)
    - November 4, 1926
      - Draft Minutes and A-E2 (Box 20)
      - F2-Q3 (Box 20)
    - December 9, 1926
      - Draft Minutes and A-C2 (Box 20)
      - D2-G2 (Box 20)
      - H2-P3 (Box 20)
    - January 6, 1927 (Box 20)
    - February 11, 1927
      - Draft Minutes and A-R2 (Box 20)
      - S2-Z3 (Box 20)
    - March 25, 1927
      - Draft Minutes and A-F2 (Box 20)
      - G2-P3 (Box 20)
    - April 22, 1927 (Box 20)
    - May 27, 1927 (Box 20)
    - June 17, 1927 (Box 20)
    - June 24, 1927 (Box 20)
    - September 30, 1927 (Box 21)
      - Draft Minutes and A-P (Box 21)
      - Q-S3 (Box 21)
      - Supporting papers for exhibit I. (Box 21)
    - October 27, 1927
      - Draft Minutes and A-Q2 (Box 21)
      - R2-S2 (Box 21)
      - T2-Q3 (Box 21)
    - December 2, 1927
      - Draft Minutes and A-U (Box 21)
      - V-L3 (Box 21)
    - January 6, 1928
      - Draft Minutes and A-Z (Box 21)
      - A2-M3 (Box 21)
    - February 3, 1928
      - Draft Minutes and A-C2 (Box 21)
      - D2-M3 (Box 21)
    - March 29, 1928
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 21)
      - I-O2 (Box 21)
      - Investment Record Book (Box 21)
      - P2-R4 (Box 21)
      - S4-G5 (Box 21)
    - April 24, 1928 (Box 22)
      - Draft Minutes and A-S2 (Box 22)
      - T2-W3 (Box 22)
    - May 25, 1928
      - Draft Minutes and A-E2 (Box 22)
      - F2-Z3 (Box 22)
    - June 15, 1928
      - Draft Minutes and A-G2 (Box 22)
      - H2-K4 (Box 22)
    - September 21, 1928
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 22)
      - D-Z (Box 22)
      - A2-Q2 (Box 22)
      - R2-F3 (Box 22)
      - G3-F5 (Box 22)
    - October 26, 1928
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 22)
      - D-V (Box 22)
      - W-L2 (Box 22)
      - M2-S2 (Box 22)
      - T2-S3 (Box 22)
    - November 23, 1928 (Box 23)
    - December 21, 1928
      - Draft Minutes and A-W (Box 23)
      - X-M3 (Box 23)
    - January 11, 1929 (Box 23)
    - January 21, 1929
      - Draft Minutes and A-W (Box 23)
      - X-N3 (Box 23)
    - February 21, 1929
      - Draft Minutes and A-S (Box 23)
      - T-I3 (Box 23)
    - March 29, 1929
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 23)
      - K-T3 (Box 23)
    - April 26, 1929
      - Draft Minutes and A-R (Box 23)
      - S-C3 (Box 23)
    - May 24, 1929 (Box 23)
    - June 14, 1929
      - Draft Minutes and A-Z (Box 23)
      - A2-J4 (Box 23)
    - October 4, 1929 (Box 24)
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 24)
      - I-M2 (Box 24)
      - N2-V2 (Box 24)
      - W2-E4 (Box 24)
      - F4-W4 (Box 24)
      - A5-Z5 (Box 24)
    - November 1, 1929
      - Secretary's File (Box 24)
      - Draft Minutes and A-Q (Box 24)
      - R-N3 (Box 24)
    - December 6, 1929
      - Secretary's File (Box 24)
      - Draft Minutes and Exhibits (Box 24)
    - January 10, 1930
      - Secretary's File (Box 24)
      - Draft Minutes and Exhibits (Box 24)
    - February 7, 1930
      - Secretary's File (Box 24)
      - Draft Minutes and Exhibits (Box 24)
    - March 7, 1930
      - Secretary's File (Box 24)
      - Draft Minutes and Exhibits (Box 24)
    - April 4, 1930
      - Secretary's File (Box 24)
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 24)
      - E-B3 (Box 24)
    - May 9, 1930 (Box 25)
      - Secretary's File (Box 25)
      - Draft Minutes and A-S (Box 25)
      - T-L3 (Box 25)
    - June 20, 1930
      - Secretary's File (Box 25)
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 25)
      - J-N2 (Box 25)
      - O2-V3 (Box 25)
    - September 26, 1930
      - Secretary's File (Box 25)
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 25)
      - D-V (Box 25)
      - W (Box 25)
      - X-A2 (Box 25)
      - B2-H2 (Box 25)
      - I2-C4 (Box 25)
    - October 4, 1930 (Box 25)
    - November 14, 1930
      - Secretary's File (Box 25)
      - Draft Minutes and A-F (Box 25)
      - G-Z (Box 25)
      - A2-R3 (Box 25)
    - December 12, 1930 (Box 26)
      - Secretary's File (Box 26)
      - Draft Minutes and Exhibits (Box 26)
  - 1931-1940
    - January 23, 1931
      - Secretary's File (Box 26)
      - Draft Minutes and A-V (Box 26)
      - W-T3 (Box 26)
    - February 27, 1931
      - Secretary's File (Box 26)
      - Draft Minutes and Exhibits (Box 26)
    - March 27, 1931
      - Secretary's File (Box 26)
      - Draft Minutes and A-M (Box 26)
      - N-G2 (Box 26)
    - April 30, 1931
      - Secretary's File (Box 26)
      - Draft Minutes and A-W (Box 26)
      - Y-K3 (Box 26)
    - May 29, 1931
      - Draft Minutes and A-F2 (Box 26)
    - June 19, 1931
      - Secretary's File (Box 26)
      - Draft Minutes and F-G (Box 26)
      - H-X2 (Box 26)
    - September 25, 1931
      - Secretary's File (Box 26)
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 26)
      - H-K (Box 26)
      - L-P (Box 26)
      - Q-N3 (Box 27)
    - November 6, 1931
      - Secretary's File (Box 27)
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 27)
      - E-F (Box 27)
      - G-U (Box 27)
      - V-O2 (Box 27)
      - P2-G3 (Box 27)
    - December 11, 1931
      - Secretary's File (Box 27)
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 27)
      - I-P2 (Box 27)
    - January 29, 1932
      - Secretary's File (Box 27)
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 27)
      - F-S (Box 27)
      - T-C3 (Box 27)
    - February 26, 1932
      - Secretary's File (Box 27)
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 27)
      - I-H2 (Box 27)
    - March 25, 1932
      - Secretary's File (Box 27)
      - Draft Minutes and A-F (Box 27)
      - G-X2 (Box 27)
    - April 29, 1932
      - Draft Minutes and A-S (Box 27)
      - T-N2 (Box 27)
    - May 27, 1932
      - Draft Minutes and A-U (Box 27)
      - V-V2 (Box 27)
    - June 17, 1932 (Box 28)
      - Draft Minutes and A-K (Box 28)
      - L-S2 (Box 28)
    - September 30, 1932
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 28)
      - D-F (Box 28)
      - G-G2 (Box 28)
      - H2-M3 (Box 28)
    - October 28, 1932
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 28)
      - D-E (Box 28)
      - F (Box 28)
      - G-J2 (Box 28)
      - K2-W2 (Box 28)
    - November 25, 1932 (Box 28)
    - December 30, 1932
      - Draft Minutes and A-L (Box 28)
      - M-S2 (Box 28)
    - January 13, 1933 (Box 28)
    - January 27, 1933
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 28)
      - F-I2 (Box 28)
    - February 24, 1933 (Box 28)
    - March 31, 1933 (Box 28)
    - April 28, 1933 (Box 28)
    - May 19, 1933 (Box 29)
    - June 16, 1933
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 29)
      - E-M2 (Box 29)
    - July 17, 1933 (Box 29)
    - August 26, 1933 (Box 29)
    - September 22, 1933
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 29)
      - D-H (Box 29)
      - I-O (Box 29)
      - P-V2 (Box 29)
    - October 20, 1933
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 29)
      - J-Q1 (Box 29)
    - December 1, 1933
      - Draft Minutes and A-M (Box 29)
      - N-I3 (Box 29)
    - February 16, 1934
      - Draft Minutes and A-B (Box 29)
      - C (Box 29)
      - D-G3 (Box 29)
    - March 30, 1934 (Box 30)
      - Draft Minutes and A-M (Box 30)
      - N-P2 (Box 30)
    - April 27, 1934
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 30)
      - K-Q2 (Box 30)
    - May 18, 1934 (Box 30)
    - June 15, 1934
      - Draft Minutes and A-N (Box 30)
      - O-S2 (Box 30)
    - August 31, 1934
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 30)
      - J-R (Box 30)
      - S-D3 (Box 30)
    - September 28, 1934
      - Draft Minutes and A-P (Box 30)
      - Q-R (Box 30)
      - S-M2 (Box 30)
    - November 2, 1934
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 30)
      - D-E (Box 30)
      - F-N2 (Box 30)
    - November 19, 1934 (Box 30)
    - December 14, 1932 (Box 31)
      - Draft Minutes and A-L (Box 31)
      - M-E3 (Box 31)
    - January 4, 1935 (Box 31)
    - January 25, 1935
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 31)
      - I-M2 (Box 31)
    - March 1, 1935
      - Draft Minutes and A-L (Box 31)
      - M-V2 (Box 31)
    - March 29, 1935
      - Draft Minutes and A-S (Box 31)
      - T-N2 (Box 31)
    - April 26, 1935
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 31)
      - F-O2 (Box 31)
    - May 31, 1935
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 31)
      - H-J3 (Box 31)
    - June 14, 1935
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 31)
      - K-L2 (Box 31)
    - July 26, 1935
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 31)
      - H-U2 (Box 31)
    - September 27, 1935 (Box 32)
      - Draft Minutes and A-B (Box 32)
      - C (Box 32)
      - D-M (Box 32)
      - N-O (Box 32)
      - P-U2 (Box 32)
    - November 1, 1935
      - Draft Minutes and A-K (Box 32)
      - L-J2 (Box 32)
      - K2-M3 (Box 32)
    - November 29, 1935
      - Draft Minutes and A-K (Box 32)
      - L-Q2 (Box 32)
    - December 20, 1935
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 32)
      - F-G2 (Box 32)
    - February 28, 1936
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 32)
      - H-M2 (Box 32)
      - N2-O2 (Box 32)
      - P2-Z2 (Box 32)
      - A3-U3 (Box 32)
    - April 3, 1936 (Box 33)
      - Draft Minutes and A-L (Box 33)
      - M-T2 (Box 33)
    - April 24, 1936
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 33)
      - I-L2 (Box 33)
    - May 15, 1936 (Box 33)
    - June 19, 1936
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 33)
      - E-W (Box 33)
      - X-V3 (Box 33)
      - W3-M4 (Box 33)
    - August 7, 1936
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 33)
      - F-T2 (Box 33)
    - October 2, 1936
      - Draft Minutes and A-M (Box 33)
      - N-S (Box 33)
      - T-E2 (Box 33)
      - F2-I3 (Box 33)
    - October 30, 1936
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 34)
      - D-L (Box 34)
      - M-G3 (Box 34)
    - December 4, 1936
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 34)
      - I-Q2 (Box 34)
    - December 12, 1936 (Box 34)
    - January 22, 1937
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 34)
      - K-L3 (Box 34)
    - February 26, 1937
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 34)
      - I-L (Box 34)
      - M-N3 (Box 34)
    - March 26, 1937
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 34)
      - K-B3 (Box 34)
    - April 30, 1937
      - Draft Minutes and A-L (Box 34)
      - M-I3 (Box 34)
    - May 28, 1937 (Box 35)
      - Draft Minutes and A-L (Box 35)
      - M-I3 (Box 35)
    - June 18, 1937
      - Draft Minutes and A-K (Box 35)
      - L-N2 (Box 35)
      - O2-K3 (Box 35)
    - July 23, 1937
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 35)
      - I-D2 (Box 35)
      - E2-B3 (Box 35)
    - September 24, 1937
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 35)
      - F-I (Box 35)
      - J-A3 (Box 35)
    - October 29, 1937
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 35)
      - D-Q 1/4 (Box 35)
      - Q 1/2-F2 (Box 35)
      - G2-Appendix B (Box 35)
    - December 10, 1937 (Box 36)
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 36)
      - E (Box 36)
      - F-U (Box 36)
      - V-Y2 (Box 36)
    - January 7, 1938
      - Draft Minutes and A-P (Box 36)
      - Q-G3 (Box 36)
      - Supplement to Exhibit H, 2 folders (Box 36)
    - February 11, 1938
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 36)
      - E-V (Box 36)
      - W-B3 (Box 36)
    - March 18, 1938
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 36)
      - J-R (Box 36)
      - S-O3 (Box 36)
    - April 29, 1938
      - Draft Minutes and A-F (Box 36)
      - G-D2 (Box 36)
      - E2-R2 (Box 36)
    - May 11, 1938 (Box 37)
    - May 27, 1938
      - Draft Minutes and A-F (Box 37)
      - G-L2 (Box 37)
      - M2-T2 (Box 37)
      - U2-Z2 (Box 37)
    - June 17, 1938
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 37)
      - E-F2 (Box 37)
      - G2-C3 (Box 37)
    - July 29, 1938
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 37)
      - K-O2 (Box 37)
      - P2-U3 (Box 37)
    - August 22, 1938 (Box 37)
    - September 8, 1938 (Box 37)
    - October 7, 1938
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 37)
      - E-G (Box 37)
      - H (Box 37)
      - I-Z (Box 37)
      - A2-B2 (Box 37)
      - C2-F3 (Box 38)
      - G3-J4 (Box 38)
    - October 18, 1938
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 38)
      - E-J (Box 38)
    - October 29, 1938
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 38)
      - H-O2 (Box 38)
    - November 12, 1938 (Box 38)
    - November 23, 1938 (Box 38)
    - December 13, 1938
      - Draft Minutes and A-L (Box 38)
      - M-V (Box 38)
      - W-L3 (Box 38)
    - December 20, 1938 (Box 38)
    - December 28, 1938 (Box 38)
    - January 31, 1939
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 38)
      - I-Z (Box 38)
      - A2-Q3 (Box 38)
    - February 8, 1939 (Box 38)
    - February 24, 1939
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 38)
      - K-J2 (Box 38)
      - K2-V2 (Box 38)
    - March 8, 1939 (Box 39)
    - March 31, 1939
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 39)
      - I-Y2 (Box 39)
    - April 14, 1939 (Box 39)
    - April 28, 1939
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 39)
      - J-Z (Box 39)
      - A2-B3 (Box 39)
    - May 8, 1939 (Box 39)
    - May 26, 1939
      - Draft Minutes and A-F (Box 39)
      - G-B3 (Box 39)
    - June 16, 1939
      - Draft Minutes and A-L (Box 39)
      - M-W2 (Box 39)
    - June 26, 1939 (Box 39)
    - August 4, 1939 (Box 39)
    - August 18, 1939 (Box 39)
    - September 18, 1939 (Box 39)
    - September 27, 1939 (Box 39)
    - October 7, 1939 (Box 40)
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 40)
      - F-P (Box 40)
      - Q-R (Box 40)
      - R (cont.)-T (Box 40)
      - U-V (Box 40)
    - (cont.), October 7, 1939
      - W-Z (Box 40)
      - A2-H2 (Box 40)
      - U2-Y3 (Box 40)
      - A4-Q4 (Box 40)
    - October 21, 1939 (Box 40)
    - November 11, 1939
      - Draft Minutes and A-K (Box 40)
      - L-B3 (Box 40)
    - December 15, 1939
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 40)
      - I-W2 (Box 40)
      - X2-H4 (Box 40)
    - January 26, 1940 (Box 41)
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 41)
      - I-U (Box 41)
      - V-M3 (Box 41)
    - March 1, 1940
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 41)
      - D-K (Box 41)
      - L-N2 (Box 41)
    - March 29, 1940
      - Draft Minutes and A-K (Box 41)
      - L-X2 (Box 41)
    - April 26, 1940
      - Draft Minutes and A-L (Box 41)
      - M-Q2 (Box 41)
    - May 24, 1940
      - Draft Minutes and A-K (Box 41)
      - L-V2 (Box 41)
    - May 28, 1940 (Box 41)
    - June 14, 1940 (Box 42)
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 42)
      - J-O (Box 42)
      - P-B3 (Box 42)
    - July 13, 1940 (Box 42)
    - September 20, 1940
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 42)
      - E-G (Box 42)
      - H-J (Box 42)
      - K-N (Box 42)
      - O-Z2 (Box 42)
      - A3-R3 (Box 42)
    - October 11, 1940 (Box 42)
    - October 19, 1940 (Box 42)
    - November 12, 1940
      - Draft Minutes and A-K (Box 42)
      - M-O (Box 42)
      - P-T (Box 42)
      - U-J3 (Box 42)
    - December 13, 1940
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 42)
      - F-E2 (Box 42)
      - F2-X2 (Box 42)
  - 1941
    - January 24, 1941
      - Draft Minutes and A-J (Box 43)
      - K-W2 (Box 43)
    - February 21, 1941
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 43)
      - F-L2 (Box 43)
    - March 28, 1941
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 43)
      - J-A3 (Box 43)
    - April 25, 1941
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 43)
      - I-J2 (Box 43)
    - May 23, 1941
      - Draft Minutes and A-F (Box 43)
      - G-C3 (Box 43)
    - June 20, 1941
      - Draft Minutes and A-F (Box 43)
      - G-O (Box 43)
      - P-D3 (Box 43)
    - July 11, 1941
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 43)
      - D-F2 (Box 43)
    - July 18, 1941 (Box 43)
    - September 12, 1941
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 43)
      - H-J (Box 44)
      - K-W2 (Box 44)
    - October 15, 1941
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 44)
      - E-J (Box 44)
      - K-K3 (Box 44)
    - November 11, 1941
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 44)
      - I-Q2 (Box 44)
    - December 19, 1941
      - Draft Minutes and A-Q (Box 44)
      - R-Q2 (Box 44)
      - R2-F3 (Box 44)
  - 1942-1951
    - January 30, 1942
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 48)
      - I-Z2 (Box 48)
      - A3-P3 (Box 48)
    - February 4 and 9, 1942 (Box 48)
    - February 27, 1942
      - Draft Minutes and A-D (Box 48)
      - E-Q2 (Box 48)
    - March 27, 1942
      - Draft Minutes and A-K (Box 48)
      - L-J2 (Box 48)
    - April 24, 1942
      - Draft Minutes and A-O (Box 48)
      - P-W2 (Box 48)
    - May 16, 1942 (Box 48)
    - May 28, 1942
      - Draft Minutes and A-C (Box 48)
      - D-V (Box 48)
      - W-V2 (Box 48)
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 49)
      - H-J2 (Box 49)
      - K2-T3 (Box 49)
    - September 11, 1942
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 49)
      - H-N (Box 49)
      - N-R3 (Box 49)
    - October 16, 1942
      - Draft Minutes and A-B (Box 49)
      - C-D1/2 (Box 49)
      - E-Q (Box 49)
      - R-W3 (Box 49)
    - November 12, 1942
      - Draft Minutes and A-G (Box 49)
      - H-S2 (Box 49)
    - December 18, 1942 (Box 50)
      - Draft Minutes and A-O (Box 50)
      - P-T (Box 50)
      - U-U3 (Box 50)
    - January 29, 1943
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 50)
      - I-O3 (Box 50)
    - February 18, 1943 (Box 50)
    - April 8, 1943
      - Draft Minutes and A-I (Box 50)
      - J-B3 (Box 50)
      - C3-I3 (Box 50)
      - J3-E4 (Box 50)
    - April 30, 1943
      - Draft Minutes and A-H (Box 50)
      - I-S2 (Box 50)
    - May 28, 1943
      - Draft Minutes and A-E (Box 50)
      - F-I3 (Box 50)
    - June 11, 1943 (Box 51)
      - Draft Minutes and A-B (Box 51)